We don't know if we'd be on the same team.
不知道是否能编列在同一队
You are the clumsy one.
姊姊个性较笨拙
So I must protect you.
所以我得保护妳
Kasane is such a gentle person.
重 是温柔的人
I'll see if he is qualified
我去帮姊姊确认
to be in a relationship with you.
他是否配得上姊姊
Kasane is strong.
重 是坚强的人
It's done, Kasane.
重 好了
This is proof that you're my sister.
这是我和重是姊妹的证明
Actually, she is a little vulnerable.
其实 她有点柔弱
Kasane.
重
Kasane...
重…
She really is a great sister.
她真是一位好妹妹
You must cherish your bond with her.
妳一定很珍惜她吧
Indeed.
对啊
Do you have anyone you treasure?
妳也有珍惜的人吗
Yes.
有啊
But those two aren't as gentle as her.
不过 他们两人没这么温柔
Well, one of them is gentle.
不 一人很温柔
But the other one...
另一人就…
Is he not a gentle person?
另一人不温柔吗
That's because he once told me
因为 他曾说我
a person like me...
像妳这样的家伙…
What did he say about you?
他说妳什么
Weird, I can't remember.
真奇怪 我突然忘了
Behave and come with us.
乖乖跟我们走吧
SCARLET NEXUS
《绯红结系》
♫Felling of tiredness is losing yourself♫
倦怠感 losing yourself
♫How do you still create a relationship each other♫
尚未找到建立关系的方法吗
♫It’s my awkward friend’s fault♫
有个麻烦的朋友
♫Until death, wanting someone somewhere to embrace me♫
至死都在寻求某人的拥抱
♫While the devil is not here and between the chaos♫
在得以喘息的混沌虚无之间
♫Aiming between win and lose♫
以输赢之间为目标
♫Not to be running out of patience for now I’m trying to be careful♫
注意别让信任走向尽头 务必小心
♫You'll see I'm always on your side♫
You'll see I'm always on your side
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
今天仍拼命地联系着
♫You’re frigid and your roller coaster inside the brain♫
你脑中那冷感的轨道
♫The grungy days and the unprecedented catastrophy♫
摇滚的日子未曾有过的浩劫
♫Where is the glory buried♫
光荣早已埋葬在某处
♫The lonely monster in a moment♫
这一瞬间寂寞孤独的野兽
♫The bullet shot by the machinegun goes parallelly♫
与机关枪射出的子弹并列
♫To pierce with the theory♫
射穿所有世间道理
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
今天仍拼命地联系着
♫The bullet shot by the machinegun goes parallelly♫
与机关枪射出的子弹并列
♫It’s the same today To connect vividly♫
今天也仍在一起 清晰地联系着
♫You’re frigid and the theory in the brain♫
你那脑中冷感的正义
NAOMI AND ALICE
(直见与艾丽斯)
Are you sure?
确定没错
I'm certain of it.
没错
But I don't understand why they are transporting Others created from humans.
不过 我不懂为何运送出 由人类变成的怪异
If this is Major General Fubuki's order,
如果是吹雪连队长下的命令
there must be a reason behind it.
应该是有什么原因
If and only if that order came from Major General Fubuki.
前提是那真的是吹雪下的命令
Sister...
姊姊…
Is it behind this door?
就在那扇门后吗
Wataru?
渡
Communication has been cut off in this area.
这里似乎被切断通讯功能了
I see.
这样啊
LOCKED
(上锁)
UNLOCKED
(开锁)
Don't worry, there is no one inside.
放心 里面没人
Is this the inside of Arahabaki?
这里就是荒吐神的内部吗
It seems different from the time when I was an intern.
跟之前实习时的感觉 完全不同
Arahabaki is several floors below Suoh.
因为荒吐神位于苏芳地下好几层
What you saw, Hanabi, was probably the upper areas known to the public.
花火妳看到的是 早已公开的上层部分吧
I think this is the secure site that controls Arahabaki.
我想这里应该是控制荒吐神 被称之为控制层的地方
Are you all right?
没事吧
I'm all right.
我没事…
Sorry about earlier. You used up too much energy to get us here just now.
抱歉 抵达这里之前 让鲁卡消耗太多脑力
We were being pursued by troops just now.
因为有许多士兵在追我们嘛
That was the only way out.
这也是没办法的事
Yuito,
别管我了 结人
I'm more worried about you.
我比较担心你
Me?
担心我
-My head doesn't hurt now. -No.
-我的头已经不痛了 -不
I mean what the Chief said.
我问的是本部长的事
I've never got into a serious argument with my brother until now.
至今 我从未跟哥哥认真吵过架
So I was a little concerned.
毕竟 会有点顾虑…
My brother decided to take over my father's work since he was a little kid.
从小 哥哥就决定 要继承爸爸的工作
I'm nothing like him.
跟我完全不同
My brother acted on his own belief.
哥哥是遵从自己的信念而行动
And that makes his actions even more unforgivable.
所以 才更无法原谅
I know you are brothers...
就算是兄弟…
No, it's actually harder for brothers to understand each other.
不 因为是兄弟才更难以互相理解
My brother's decisions always confuse me too.
我也总是无法理解 自家哥哥的想法
I bet Major General Karen is even more unpredictable than my brother.
卡连前连队长 应该比我哥更难懂吧
Indeed.
就是啊
Tsugumi, can you spot the access point within Arahabaki?
鸫 能看得出荒吐神中 类似连结点的地方吗
This place is too huge, I can't get a clear view.
这里太宽阔 不是很清楚
But there is a location where the routes converge.
但有个类似集中线路回路的地方
All right, that's where we must go.
好 去那里看看吧
Are these all of them?
全部就这些了吧
Yes.
是的
Contact Chief Sumeragi.
跟皇本部长联络
Who are these people?
这些人是谁
Don't worry, there is nothing to be feared.
放心吧 没什么好怕的
Right?
对吧
Are you...
妳是…
Yes, I no longer feel fear.
对 我已经不害怕了
Who is it?
是谁
Kasane Randall?
重兰德尔
What is she doing here?
她为何在这
Kasane!
重
What is your motive of doing this?
你们这么做的目的是什么
We are carrying out our order.
我们正在执行任务
We transported them here to make final adjustments to our Other weapons.
为了帮怪异兵器做最后的调整 才将它们搬运出来
Perhaps our superior thinks it's time to finally put these to practical uses.
可能是上层判断 用于实战的时机到了吧
You plan to use my sister as a weapon.
你们打算将姊姊当作兵器并利用她
I will never allow that.
这种事 我绝不允许
We are in charge of the research facility.
我们是研究设施的负责人
We take orders from Major General Fubuki.
听从吹雪连队长的指示行动
But Fubuki is nowhere to be found.
但似乎没看到吹雪的身影
Major General Fubuki has other important matters to see to.
吹雪连队长 要忙其他要务
I find it hard to believe Fubuki would give such order.
我很难相信 吹雪会下这种命令
Kasane.
重
Sister.
姊姊
Don't you worry, I will keep you safe.
放心吧 我会保护妳
No, you need to run now.
不行 快逃
These people are lying to you.
这些人在说谎
I just overheard them talking about contacting Chief Sumeragi.
我刚才听到 他们要联络皇本部长
I get it now.
原来如此
They aren't following orders from Major General Fubuki.
他们不是听从吹雪连队长的命令
They are working for Chief Sumeragi.
而是听从皇本部长的命令
I don't know what you're planning,
我不知道你们有何企图
but I won't let you use my sister as a weapon.
但我不会让你们利用姊姊
Kasane...
重…
Chief Sumeragi.
皇本部长
This is the best opportunity to gauge the Other weapons' power.
这是见识怪异兵器力量的好机会
Roger.
遵命
We've confirmed Fubuki Spring's location.
确认吹雪诗宾的所在位置
-Carry out the mission now. -Yes.
-立刻执行任务 -是
Fubuki, you are Suoh's enemy.
吹雪 你是苏芳的敌人
But I didn't expect you to hide this trick up your sleeve.
没想到你藏了这等好东西
Put them to good use. We can deal significant damage to Seiran with these.
好好利用 必能给青蓝巨大损伤
Thank you, Major General Fubuki.
我向你道谢 吹雪连队长
You must be OSF soldiers from Suoh.
你们是… 苏芳的怪伐军吧
Sister, are you hurt?
姊姊 妳没受伤吧
We must leave this place together.
我们一起逃走吧
Kasane...
重…
-Are you all right? -Yes.
-没事吧 -没事
-Is it okay?
-可以吧 -是
Eliminate these people.
将这些人全部消灭
Sister...
姊姊…
Kasane, get out of there now!
重 快点离开那里
Sister, can you hear me? Sister!
姊姊 听得到吗 姊姊
It's me, Kasane!
是我 我是重
No!
不行…
Sister!
姊姊
Wake up!
快清醒啊
Those people...
那是…
Togetsu.
渡月
Positive ID on Kasane Randall.
确认重兰德尔
Commencing brain retrieval.
开始回收其脑部
What is going on now?
现在是什么情况
Wait, we don't want to fight you!
等等 我们不打算与你们为敌
These people are using their allies to attack.
那些人 利用伙伴攻击敌人吗
They can't tell enemies from allies. This is bad.
攻击不分敌我 真麻烦
Kyoka!
镜花
Over here.
这边
Not a chance!
休想
Do it.
动手
Kasane!
重…
You...
你是…
Sister.
姊姊
I finally understand why I was turned into this form.
我终于知道 为何变成这幕模样了
It is so that I can protect you, Kasane.
一定是为了保护重
Run. I'll distract that thing.
快逃 我来引开他
No. even with your Other power,
不行 就算姊姊拥有怪异的力量
I can't leave you behind.
但我不能丢下妳一人
I'm not alone here.
我不是一个人
Everyone else will help me.
大家都会协助我
No.
不行
Stop it, Sister.
住手 姊姊
I'll figure out a solution, so please...
我会想办法找到出路的 所以…
I'm sorry you're always so worried about me.
抱歉 总是让妳陪着我
So let me be the cool Big Sister for once.
这种时候就让我当个帅气的姊姊吧
No, you should come with us.
不行 我们一起逃吧
Where can I possibly go?
能逃去哪呢
Arashi, I leave Kasane to you.
岚 重 就拜托妳了
Yes.
好
Sister!
姊姊
Let's go, Kasane.
走吧 重
Please, stay still.
拜托 别乱动喔
Sister!
姊姊
I know you're still recovering,
就算伤势尚未痊愈
but this is too weak even for you.
但你也太快被打倒了
Sorry.
抱歉…
Suoh is at the end of their rope.
看来苏芳也到极限了
To think they actually sent hitmen.
竟然使出暗杀手段
They are getting impatient.
真是性急
Let's see if you know something useful.
让我看看有没有什么内幕
Alice!
艾丽斯
Sister.
姊姊
Wake up, Sister.
醒醒啊 姊姊
No, this can't be happening.
不要 我不要
Sister...
姊姊…
Oh my, you really are a cry baby, Kasane.
真是的 重真的很爱哭呢
Sister.
姊姊
Why did you come back? It's still too dangerous to be here.
妳怎么回来了 可能还很危险呢
But I'm glad all of you are safe now.
不过太好了 你们没事
Sister, it must hurt a lot. You're covered in wounds.
姊姊 很痛吧 妳受了好重的伤
Actually, I don't feel any pain anymore.
其实 我已经感觉不到痛觉了
After I was turned into this thing,
变成这副模样
after taking medicine made from human brains,
使用人脑做成的药物
death is the only thing I seek.
我一直想死
But I've made it this far.
但还是活到今天
I'm so happy.
真是太好了
Sister...
姊姊…
In the end, I get to live like a human
最后 终于活得像人类一般
despite having the form of Other.
即便变成怪异 能以人的身分…
No...
不…
Thank you, Kasane.
谢谢妳 重
Live on for me.
连我的份 好好活下去
Sister!
姊姊…
Don't go. Don't leave me behind.
别走 别丢下我啊
You...
妳是…
-Alice. -Karen?
-艾丽斯 -卡连
Did I fail again?
我又… 失败了吗
Major General Karen.
卡连连队长
Kasane! Watch out!
重 危险
I'll rewrite it as many times as it takes.
改写几次都无所谓
Yuito.
结人…
Don't go!
别跑
Karen copied Kasane's power.
卡连 复制了重的能力
Did he copy the Red Strings as well?
他复制了红色系线吗
What is his motive?
目的是什么
Is he going back in time to save Alice?
他打算回到过去 拯救艾丽斯吗
But there is no sign of the Red Strings being triggered.
可是 看不出来 红色系线发动的迹象
That is Arahabaki's access terminal.
这里就是荒吐神的连结终端
It looks like the one we found at Togetsu.
跟渡月一样 是椅子类型的终端
What if it happens again?
万一像当时那样…
I know the risk, but I must do this.
就算有风险 我也要做
Be careful.
小心点
It's very similar to OSF's system.
真像怪伐军的系统
It seems we can upload images here.
看样子能上传影片档案
Messages sent from Arahabaki
从荒吐神寄出的资料
will be forced on all citizens
会强制送给全国人民
regardless of age and gender,
不论其年龄及性别
and against their will.
以及其个人意愿
The people will learn about the video file.
刚才的影片档案 必定会被人民看见
Yes.
没错
People will start asking why they were given this information.
一定会有人想知道 为何告知他们这一切
But even so, I want to know
即便如此我仍想知道
how people will react after learning the truth.
人民知道后有何反应
Father, Brother.
爸爸 哥哥
I'm sorry.
抱歉我擅自这么做
But I must pave my own path.
但 我要走自己的道路
DO YOU WISH TO EXECUTE THE ORDER? YES OR NO
(确定要执行吗 是 否)
We inherited the legacy from Yakumo Sumeragi.
我们继承了八云皇的意志
We must have our revenge on the Moon.
必须对月球进行复仇
You're insane!
开什么玩笑
Even users like us can't handle the load from SAS!
就算是超脑力者 也难以承受SAS
It doesn't matter.
无法承受也无所谓
All we need is their brains and body parts.
我们需要的 只有脑和身体零件
Did it work?
顺利成功了吗
I don't think we received the message.
我们似乎没收到数据
Communication is cut off in here.
因为这里被切断通讯功能
I see.
对喔
After the people of New Himuka watch this footage,
新日向的国民看到这段影片
there will be mass protests outside.
现在外面应该引起大骚动了
This footage is a catalyst.
这段影片是个契机
We have no way to know about the future of New Himuka.
新日向之后的命运会如何 也还未可知
Let's go back.
回去吧
I want to know what's going on inside the city.
我想知道城市里的情况
Sure.
好
Stop right there.
乖乖别动
♫I'm troubled by my own yearning♫
被追求的憧憬所困
♫Unveil the blocked sun ray♫
揭开被阻挡的摇曳阳炎
♫There's a stranger in me♫
There's a stranger in me
♫That I've never seen♫
从未见过
♫I can not soar in the sky without fear♫
自己能不再恐惧翱翔高空
♫I'm spreading my wings♫
I'm spreading my wings
♫Dancing gracefully like a bird♫
华丽舞步的鸟儿
♫And gazing towards the scarlet sky♫
仰望染红的天空
♫I chased after the gust♫
追过了强风
♫The scenery spreads into the ever-changing world♫
景色蔓延在千变万化的世界里
♫Inside the intertwined brilliance♫
在交错的光芒中
♫I'm still searching for tomorrow's direction♫
持续寻找明天的行径方向
♫Tomorrow's in your hands♫
Tomorrow's in your hands
♫Don't tell me now you're afraid♫
Don't tell me now you're afraid
♫There's no time to waste♫
There's no time to waste
♫Go forward♫
前进
♫Have no fear for anything♫
不再畏惧何物
♫Now, let's go♫
走吧
♫Into a brand new day♫
Into a brand new day
ARAHABAKI'S TRAP
(荒吐神的陷阱)